Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Ballet Photographs, circa 1910-1960
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
J. Warren Perry Collection of Ballet Photographs, circa 1910-1960
Mus. Arc. 3.2
Perry, J. Warren
5 boxes (300 items)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
A collection of 300 black and white photographs of ballet dancers and choreographers, chiefly from the 1950s. Many of the photographs bear inscriptions to Dr. Perry and a very small number were accompanied by correspondence or clippings.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of J. Warren Perry, November 2004.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection has been digitized and is available in the UB Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Dr. J. Warren Perry was born in Richmond, Indiana in 1921. He earned his B.A. at DePauw University in 1944, his Master's at Northwestern University in 1952, and his Ph.D. at Northwestern in 1955. Dr. Perry has been on the faculties at the University of Illinois at Chicago, Northwestern Medical School, and the University of Chicago. He was also employed as deputy assistant commissioner for research and training in the Vocational Rehabilitation Administration at the Department of Health, Education and Welfare in Washington, D.C. Dr. Perry is the founder of the School of Health Related Professions (now the School of Public Health and Health Professions) at the University at Buffalo, The State University of New York. He served as dean of the school from its founding in 1967 until 1977.
Dr. Perry has devoted much of his life to supporting the arts. Before moving to Buffalo he was one of the founders of the Lyric Opera Company in Chicago. Since arriving in Buffalo Dr. Perry has served as chairman or board member for several local organizations, including the Buffalo Philharmonic, Community Music School, Theodore Roosevelt Inaugural National Historic Site, Artpark, and Friends of the Center for the Arts. The numerous awards granted to honor Dr. Perry's contributions to the community include the Buffalo Arts Councils' Supporter of the Arts award, the Buffalo Distinguished Citizen Award, and national Outstanding Philanthropist Award.
Scope and Content Note
The J. Warren Perry Collection of Ballet Photographs, ca. 1910-1960 is a complement to the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971. It consists of 300 black and white photographs of many of the most significant ballet dancers of the mid-twentieth century, especially the 1950s. Many of the photographs bear inscriptions from the dancers to Dr. Perry. The collection also contains the photographic work of the most important dance photographers of the first half of the twentieth century, including Herman Mishkin, Witzel, Maurice Seymour, Fred Fehl, Roger Wood, Houston Rogers, Martha Swope, Michael Dunne, George Platt Lynes, and Walter E. Owen.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series:
I. People. Arranged alphabetically by person's name.
II. Productions. Arranged alphabetically by city location.
Container List
- People, circa 1910-1960, I.; Boxes 1-4 (Items 1-250)
  Arranged alphabetically by personal name.
  - Diana Adams sur les pointes, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB001)
  - Diana Adams as Iseult in Picnic at Tintagel, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 1, Item JWPB002)
  - Diana Adams and André Eglevsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB003)
  - Diana Adams and Herbert Bliss in Symphony in C, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 1, Item JWPB004)
  - Diana Adams and Arthur Mitchell rehearsing Agon, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Swope, Martha (Box 1, Item JWPB005)
  - Diana Adams and Arthur Mitchell rehearsing Agon, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Swope, Martha (Box 1, Item JWPB006)
  - Alicia Alonso as Odette in Swan Lake, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 1, Item JWPB007)
  - Alicia Alonso, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB008)
  - Alicia Alonso as the Black Swan (Odile) in Swan Lake, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 1, Item JWPB009)
  - Alicia Alonso and Ygor Youskevitch as Odette and Prince Siegfried in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB010)
  - Alicia Alonso and Ygor Youskevitch in the Black Swan Pas de deux from Swan Lake, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB011)
  - Alicia Alonso as Giselle, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB012)
  - Alicia Alonso and Ygor Youskevitch in Giselle, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 1, Item JWPB013)
  - Ruth Andersen, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Hope, Constance (Box 1, Item JWPB014)
  - Verner Andersen, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Hope, Constance (Box 1, Item JWPB015)
  - Sir Frederick Ashton as Kastchei in the Firebird, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 1, Item JWPB016)
  - George Balanchine, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB017)
  - George Balanchine, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB018)
  - Svetlana Beriosova and Michael Somes as Antigone and Creon, 1959, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB019)
  - Svetlana Beriosova and David Blair in Prince of the Pagodas, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 1, Item JWPB020)
  - Svetlana Beriosova and David Blair in Prince of the Pagodas, Act. II, scene ii, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Jones, Anthony Armstrong (Box 1, Item JWPB021)
  - Svetlana Beriosova and Philip Chatfield in The shadow, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Baron, 1906 (Box 1, Item JWPB022)
  - Herbert Bliss in Western Symphony, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB023)
  - Herbert Bliss and Diana Adams in Western Symphony, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB024)
  - Todd Bolender, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB025)
  - Todd Bolender in Western Symphony?, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB026)
  - Todd Bolender in Western Symphony with unidentified female dancer, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Bascome, Radford (Box 1, Item JWPB027)
  - Irina Borowska, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB028)
  - Oleg Briansky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB029)
  - Oleg Briansky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB030)
  - Oleg Briansky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB031)
  - Eric Braun, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Valente, Alfredo (Box 1, Item JWPB032)
  - Erik Bruhn, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB033)
  - Erik Bruhn and Lupe Serrano, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB034)
  - Lucia Chase as the Step-Mother in Fall River Legend, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB035)
  - Yvonne Chouteau as Snow Queen in The Nutcracker, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB036)
  - Yvonne Chouteau in Balanchine's Pas de Trois, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB037)
  - Yvonne Chouteau, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB038)
  - Pauline Clayden and Alexander Grant in Daphnis and Chloe, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Baron, 1906 (Box 1, Item JWPB039)
  - Jacques D'Amboise as Mac in The Filling Station, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB040)
  - Jacques D'Amboise, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB041)
  - Jacques D'Amboise and Lupe Serrano as solo dancers in Strauss' Der Fledermaus, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Mélançon, Louis (Box 1, Item JWPB042)
  - Jacques D'Amboise, Diana Adams, and Yvonne Mounsey in Picnic at Tintagel, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB043)
  - Alexandra Danilova as Odette in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB044)
  - Joe and Donna Del Edwards, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB045)
  - Joe and Donna Del Edwards, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB046)
  - Agnes DeMille, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; McBean, Angus, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB047)
  - Agnes DeMille as the Cowgirl in Rodeo, 1942, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB048)
  - Anton Dolin, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB049)
  - Anton Dolin as Petrouchka, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB050)
  - Anton Dolin and Nathalie Krassovska in Giselle, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB051)
  - Anton Dolin and Alicia Markova, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB052)
  - Mary Drage and Meriel Evans in Les Patineurs, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 1, Item JWPB053)
  - André Egelvsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB054)
  - André Egelvsky, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 1, Item JWPB055)
  - André Egelvsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Bascome, Radford (Box 1, Item JWPB056)
  - André Egelvsky in A la Francaix, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955 (Box 1, Item JWPB057)
  - Violetta Elvin in Sylvia, after 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 1, Item JWPB058)
  - Violetta Elvin as Blue Bird in Sleeping Beauty, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 1, Item JWPB059)
  - Margot Fonteyn portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB060)
  - Margot Fonteyn portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB061)
  - Margot Fonteyn portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB062)
  - Margot Fonteyn as Giselle, 1960, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB063)
  - Margot Fonteyn as the Firebird, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB064)
  - Margot Fonteyn as Péri, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB065)
  - Margot Fonteyn as Princess Aurora in Sleeping Beauty, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB066)
  - Margot Fonteyn and Michael Somes as Princess Aurora and Prince Florimund in Sleeping Beauty, after 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB067)
  - Margot Fonteyn and Michael Somes in La Péri, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB068)
  - Margot Fonteyn and Michael Somes in La Péri, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB069)
  - Margot Fonteyn as The Ballerina in Petrouchka, 1960, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 2, Item JWPB070)
  - Margot Fonteyn as The Ballerina in Petrouchka, with Peter Clegg as The Moor, and Alexander Grant as Petrouchka, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 2, Item JWPB071)
  - Margot Fonteyn and Michael Somes in Sylvia, Act III, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB072)
  - Margot Fonteyn and Michael Somes in the Birthday Offering, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB073)
  - Frederic Franklin as Stanley in Streetcar Named Desire, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB074)
  - Frederic Franklin and Mia Slavenska in Streetcar Named Desire, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB075)
  - Frederic Franklin and Mia Slavenska in Coppelia, Act III, 1948?, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB076)
  - Kenneth Gillespie, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB077)
  - Kenneth Gillespie in Raymonda, 1958, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB078)
  - Martha Graham, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Witzel (Box 2, Item JWPB079)
  - José Greco, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB080)
  - José Greco, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB081)
  - Melissa Hayden as Clorinda in The Duel (also know as The Combat), 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB082)
  - Melissa Hayden, Tanaquil LeClercq, and Nicholas Magallanes in Illuminations, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB083)
  - Robert Helpmann, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB084)
  - Alan Howard, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB085)
  - Alan Howard, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB086)
  - Alan Howard, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Lake, George (Box 2, Item JWPB087)
  - Rowena Jackson in Ballet Imperial, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB088)
  - Rowena Jackson and Michael Somes in Le Lac des Cygnes, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB089)
  - Jillana, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB090)
  - Kenneth Johnson, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB091)
  - Nora Kaye, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB092)
  - Nora Kaye, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB093)
  - Nora Kaye in Pillar of Fire, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB094)
  - Nora Kaye as Odette in Swan Lake, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB095)
  - Nora Kaye and Erik Bruhn in The Black Swan Pas de deux, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB096)
  - Nora Kaye and Erik Bruhn in Giselle, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB097)
  - Nora Kaye and Lucia Chase in Pillar of Fire, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB098)
  - Lincoln Kirstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB099)
  - Ruth Ann Koesun in Offenbach in the Underworld, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB100)
  - Nathalie Krassovska and Louis Godfrey in Scheherazade, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB101)
  - Nora Kovach and Istvan Rabovsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB102)
  - Nora Kovach and Istvan Rabovsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB103)
  - John Kriza, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB104)
  - John Kriza as Billy the Kid, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Avedon, Richard (Box 2, Item JWPB105)
  - John Kriza as Tancredi in The Duel, 1959, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB106)
  - John Kriza and Melissa Hayden in The Duel, 1953, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB107)
  - John Kriza and Nora Kaye in Offenbach in the Underworld, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB108)
  - Hugh Laing as the Prodigal Son, after 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB109)
  - Maryon Lane and Leslie Edwards in Noctambules, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Dunne, Michael (Box 2, Item JWPB110)
  - Yurek Lazowsky in Rodeo, 1955, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 2, Item JWPB111)
  - Tanaquil LeClercq in La Valse, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 2, Item JWPB112)
  - Tanaquil LeClercq, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955 (Box 2, Item JWPB113)
  - Tanaquil Le Clercq in Illuminations, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB114)
  - José Limón, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB115)
  - José Limón, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB116)
  - José Limón, Pauline Koner, Lucas Hoving, and Betty Jones in The Moor's Pavane, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB117)
  - José Limón as the Traitor and Lucas Hoving as The Leader in The Traitor, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB118)
  - Anya Linden (Sainsbury), undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB119)
  - Anya Linden (Sainsbury) as Princess Aurora in Sleeping Beauty, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB120)
  - Anya Linden (Sainsbury) as the Poor girl and Desmond Doyle as the Rich Man in Noctambules, 1956, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Rogers, Houston (Box 2, Item JWPB121)
  - Eugene Loring as Billy the Kid, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB122)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as the Second Intruder in The Cage, 1951, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB123)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as Orpheus and Francisco Moncion as the Dark Angel in Orpheus, 1948, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB124)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as Orpheus and Francisco Moncion as the Dark Angel in Orpheus, 1948, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB125)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as Orpheus and Maria Tallchief as Eurydice in Orpheus, 1948, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB126)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as The Poet in Illuminations, 1950, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB127)
  - Nicholas Magallanes in Square Dance, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Moffett, George (Box 2, Item JWPB128)
  - Nicholas Magallanes as the Poet in The Unicorn, the gorgon, and the Manticore, 1957, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JWPB129)
  - Alicia Markova as the Sugar Plum Fairy in the Nutcracker, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 3, Item JWPB130)
  - Alicia Markova as Giselle, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 3, Item JWPB131)
  - Alicia Markova in Sylphides, 1954, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB132)
  - Alicia Markova, 1952, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Heinrich, Annemarie (Box 3, Item JWPB133)
  - Ruth Mata and Eugene Hari, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Seymour, Maurice, 1904- (Box 3, Item JWPB134)
  - Francisco Moncion as Prince Ivan in the Firebird, 1949, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB135)
  - Francisco Moncion as the Prodigal Son, 1950s, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB136)
  - Francisco Moncion as Midas in The Triumph of Bacchus and Ariadne, 1948, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB137)
  - Francisco Moncion as the Dark Angel, Nicholas Magallanes as Orpheus, and Maria Tallchief as Eurydice in Orpheus, 1948, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB138)
  - Francisco Moncion and Yvonne Mounsey in the Prodigal Son, 1950s, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB139)
  - Yvonne Mounsey as the Siren in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB140)
  - Yvonne Mounsey as the Siren in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB141)
  - Yvonne Mounsey as the Siren in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB142)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Francisco Moncion in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB143)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Hugh Laing in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB144)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Hugh Laing in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Owen, Walter E., 1896-1963 (Box 3, Item JWPB145)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Francisco Moncion in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 3, Item JWPB146)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Francisco Moncion in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 3, Item JWPB147)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Francisco Moncion in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Wood, Roger (Box 3, Item JWPB148)
  - Yvonne Mounsey and Francisco Moncion in the Prodigal Son, undated, 1 black and white photograph, 8 x 10 inches; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JWPB149)